luceosolutions.com 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Luceo Solutions | Recruitment Software | Applicant Tracking System

### Overview

Welcome to the Luceo Solutions, LLC ("Luceo Solutions”) website. Below you will find our Privacy Policy regarding any personal information that you may supply to us through www.luceosolutions.com. Luceo Solutions is committed to protecting your privacy and the personal information that you submit through the Internet.

By accessing www.luceosolutions.com, you acknowledge and fully understand this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions posted on this website.

Please note that this website is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 on this website. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of 13 on the website, we will delete the information from our records.

### Personal Information We Collect

You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) on this website. Here are some of the ways you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit.

  * Request a Demo: If you request a demonstration of our products, we ask for your information such as your name, telephone number, and email address so that we can contact you in order to run a demo.
  * Contact Us: If you email us through a "Contact Us” link on this website, we may ask for your information such as your name and email address so that we can respond to your questions and comments.

Unless you ask us not to do so, we may use your information to contact you via email or telephone in the future to tell you about specials, new products or changes to this Privacy Policy.

We also may transfer the personal information we collect on this website to other countries where we do business, but we will do so only for the purposes described above. When we transfer the information to the other countries, we will protect the information as described here unless otherwise required by applicable law. 

We do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors to any third party outside of our organization, except as described further in this policy. We may share information provided by our visitors to this website with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or by legal process; (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials; or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. In addition, we reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Any information provided to Luceo Solutions is treated with care and discretion. Luceo Solutions takes a proactive approach to make sure that the information is kept private and is not misused.

### Additional Policies for Job Seekers

If you submit personal information as a job seeker on one of our client websites, the use and protection of such information is governed by a Privacy Policy posted on that particular web page. 

### Other Sites

Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personal information. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits its residents to request and receive information about a business’ disclosure of certain categories of personal information to other companies for their use in direct marketing. If you are a California resident, you can request a copy of this information from Luceo Solutions by sending an email to [privacy@luceoUS.com](mailto:privacy@luceoUS.com) or a letter to Luceo Solutions at:

Luceo Solutions  
Attn: Customer Service  
200 N. LaSalle, Suite 1100  
Chicago, IL 60601

Please include your name and email address in email requests, and your name and postal address in mail requests. 

### Safe Harbor

Luceo Solutions has certified its adherence to the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Principles in connection with the U.S. implementation of the European Union Data Protection Directive. For more information about the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles and to view the certification for Luceo Solutions, visit the U.S. Department of this certification. In addition, Luceo Solutions is a member of the BBBOnLine U.S./E.U. Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution program. Please consult the BBBOnLine website for more information concerning the BBBOnLine privacy programs and dispute resolution procedures.

### Updates to Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will post a notice on our website to notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Statement, if you would like to update information we have about you, or if you would like to opt out of future contacts from us, please contact us via email at [support@luceoUS.com](mailto:support@luceoUS.com).
